weeks	O
.	O
Empire	B-location
State	I-location
Building	I-location
.	O
Pretty	O
bad	O
storm	O

Playboy	B-corporation
-	O
10	O
October	O
2010	O
Slovenia	B-location
:	O
Playboy	B-corporation
-	O

my	O
time	O
now	O
btwn	O
SF	B-location
and	O
San	B-location
Mateo	I-location
